(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T22:39:49.133515",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
※この配信は演出により激しく点滅する場面がございます
部屋を明るくし画面から十分離れてご視聴ください
*This stream contains scenes with intense flashing lights.
Please watch in a well-lit room and stay a safe distance from the screen.
店長 兎田
[Manager: Usada]
周年記念
[Anniversary Celebration]
朝礼
[Morning Meeting]
まもなく！
[Starting Soon!]
さあ いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ！
Step right up! Welcome, welcome, welcome!
ありがとうございます ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
さあ いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ！
Step right up! Welcome, welcome!
本日はお忙しい中 数ある配信の中から
We know you're busy, but out of all the streams available today...
当配信 兎田ぺこら7周年ライブをご指名いただき ご閲覧いただき 誠にありがとうございます！
thank you so much for choosing and viewing Usada Pekora's 7th Anniversary Live!
日頃のご愛顧にお応えいたしまして 兎田ぺこらオリジナルのステージを取り揃えましてのお出迎え！
To show our gratitude for your continued support, we welcome you with a special, custom Usada Pekora stage!
お祭り騒ぎで ゲストも沢山でお送りいたします！
It's going to be a festive celebration with lots of special guests!
球の方も メダルの方も 全て超、超、超！
The pachinko balls and the slot medals are all super, super, super...
おすすめでお出迎えとなっておりますれば
...highly recommended as we welcome you!
どちらのお客様も 最後までじゃんじゃんバリバリとお楽しみくださいませ！
So to all our guests, please enjoy the show to the absolute fullest until the very end!
日頃ご自慢の右腕 左腕に より一層の磨きをかけましてで
Please warm up and polish your proud right and left arms even more,
しっかりとガッチリと コメントもしてくださいませ！
and make sure to leave plenty of enthusiastic comments!
さあ いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ！
Step right up! Welcome, welcome, welcome!
ありがとうございました！ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Now, welcome, welcome, welcome!
本日も様々な景品、グッズをご用意しております。
We have various prizes and merchandise ready for you today as well.
ぜひ本日のライブの思い出におひとついかがでしょうか。
How about one as a memento of today's live concert?
ひとつめの目玉商品は、こちら！アクリルパネル！
Our first featured item is this: the Acrylic Panel!
こちらはなんと、ホロライブEnglishのイナちゃんが描き下ろしてくれました！
This was newly illustrated by Ina-chan from hololive English!
とってもレア！とってもレア！そして、かわいいぺこら！
It's so rare, so rare! And Pekora looks super cute!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！イナ、ありがとう、イナ！
Thank you so much! Thank you so much! Ina, thank you, Ina!
ぜひとも皆さんのデスクトップの隣に置くと、良いぺこですね。
It would be great if you put it next to your desktop, peko.
２つめはこちら！ランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
Our second item is this: Random Acrylic Keychains!
イラストはまるえり先生に書いてもらいました！
The illustrations were drawn by Marueri-sensei!
めちゃめちゃかわいいぺこですね！
They are super cute, peko!
ぜひとも、なら、お揃えたくなってしまう、そんなランダムアクリルキーホルダー。
You'll definitely want to collect them all!
どれが来るかは届いてからのお楽しみぺこです。
Look forward to seeing which one you get once it arrives, peko.
３つめは、ぺこら直筆の「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ！
Third is the "No way, peko..." T-shirt handwritten by Pekora!
この暑い夏を乗り切るのにぴったりなTシャツ！
A T-shirt perfect for getting through this hot summer!
「うそぺこでしょ…」の場面がきっとある、そんな時に着たいTシャツぺこですね！
A T-shirt you'll want to wear when you have one of those "No way, peko..." moments!
４つめはトラックジャケット！
Fourth is the Track Jacket!
こちらもまた最高にかっこいいぺこですね！
This one is also incredibly cool, peko!
後ろにはキービジュアルのぺこら！
It features the key visual of Pekora on the back!
この中に「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ、そしてジャケットを羽織ってうちに行ったら最高！
It'd be awesome to wear the "No way, peko..." T-shirt inside and throw this jacket over it!
お出かけにも丁度いいぺこですね！
It's just perfect for going out, peko!
そしてなんと、なんと、フルセットをご購入の方には、さらなる特典がございます！
And surprisingly, there's an extra bonus for those who purchase the full set!
こちら！
Right here!
数量限定で、ぺこらの直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りポストカードがついてくる！
It comes with a limited-edition postcard with Pekora's handwritten signature and a foil-stamped message replica!
以上、ぜひ皆様、じゃんじゃんばりばりゲットしてください！
That's all! Please go ahead and grab yours!
兎田ぺこらに夢と希望と未来を乗せまして、
Carrying dreams, hopes, and the future on Usada Pekora,
配信終了のお声がかかりますまで、一気にじゃんじゃんばりばりと最後、最後のお時間までご視聴くださいませ！
please enjoy watching until the very end, until the broadcast is over!
Ah 潮風に誘われて
Ah, lured by the sea breeze...
はしゃぐ声 波の音 近づいてゆく
Excited voices, the sound of waves, getting closer...
Ah 高い空 白い雲
Ah, the high sky, white clouds...
まぶしい海と恋の季節
The dazzling sea and the season of love.
日に焼けた あなたが笑っていた
Suntanned, you were smiling.
たくさんの光が キラキラ
So much light is sparkling.
コイするココロで変わりだす ラッキー・デイ
A lucky day starting to change with a heart in love...
繋いだ手がほら 魔法にかかるよ
Look, our joined hands are under a magic spell.
笑ってばっかり ここは夏の国
Nothing but smiles, this is a summer land.
私をバージョンアップ！
Version up myself!
Ah 照らし出す太陽が
Ah, the shining sun...
まぶしくて かき氷 イチゴえらんで
is so dazzling, choosing strawberry shaved ice.
Ah 青い空 白い砂
Ah, blue sky, white sand...
コントラストなピンクのくち
A contrasting pink mouth...
染まってく くちびる 照れ笑い
Lips getting stained, a shy smile.
誘ってるみたいで ドキドキ
It feels like an invitation, making my heart race.
コイするココロがスピードあげてく
My heart in love is speeding up.
恋するココロが スピードあげてく
My loving heart speeds up
見つめるヒトミが 大胆になるよ
The eyes looking at you become bold
言葉はいらない 今を感じたい
No words are needed, I want to feel the present
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrade me!
夕陽を映す海はオレンジ
The ocean reflecting the sunset is orange
二人のシルエット
Our two silhouettes
足をさらう星の砂
The star-shaped sand washing away under our feet
そっと、ねえ連れてって遠くに
Softly, hey, take me far away
恋するココロは もう止まらない！
My loving heart can't be stopped anymore!
合わせた手のひら 合図を送るよ
Our joined palms send a signal
何もいらない ふたりだけの国
We don't need anything in a country of just the two of us
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrade me!
恋するココロで変わりだす ラッキー・デイ
A lucky day starting to change with my loving heart
繋いだ手がほら 魔法にかかるよ
Look, our held hands are being cast with magic
笑ってばっかり ここは夏の国
Nothing but smiles, this is a country of summer
私をバージョンアップ！
Upgrade me!
私のブランニュー・デイ！！！
My brand new day!!!
はい！みんなー！ぺこらのライブに来てくれてありぺこでしたー！
Yes! Everyone! Thank you so much for coming to Pekora's live concert!
1曲目は「私バージョンアップ！」でしたー！
The first song was "Watashi Version Up!"!
1曲目、当てた人いますかー？何のね、
Did anyone guess the first song? I wonder...
曲が来るか、みんなね、たくさん考えてくれたと思うけど、
...what song would play. I'm sure you all thought a lot about it,
まずは1曲目は「私バージョンアップ！」でした！
but the first song was "Watashi Version Up!".
ということで、今回も！兎田ぺこら、
And so, this time too! Usada Pekora's...
パチンコスロットライブ、第三弾ーーー！
Pachinko/Slot Live Part 3!!!
イェーイ！イェーイ！ということで、おやおやぺこちゃん、
Yay! Yay! And with that, "Oh my, Peko-chan,"
前回も、前々回も、パチンコスロットライブだったじゃん、
"your last and second-to-last concerts were also Pachinko/Slot Lives, right?"
何で3回目もやるんだよ！って、思いましたよね？
"Why are you doing it a third time?!" you must be thinking, right?
はい、私も、3回目はやりすぎか、
Yes, I also thought, "Is a third time a bit too much?"
流死にやりすぎてるぺこなのかな、って思ったんですけども、
"Am I doing it a bit too much, peko?" but...
こちら見てください！
Please look at this!
はい！兎田ぺこら、5周年記念ライブ、ということで！
Yes! Usada Pekora's 5th Anniversary Live!
7なんです！
It's 7!
7と言ったら、やるしかないよね！そうぺこだよね！
Speaking of 7, we've got to do it! Right, peko?
ということで、今回もやらせてください！めちゃめちゃね、良い曲、
So, please let me do it this time too! There are lots of really great songs...
たくさんあるぺこですので、絶対みんなも楽しんでもらえる、
...so I'm sure everyone will definitely have fun!
それだけは自信があるぺこなーので、是非ともお楽しみに！
I'm really confident about that, so please look forward to it!
そして、ハッシュタグのね、「兎田ぺこら5周年記念LIVE」もたくさん呟いてくださーーい！
Also, please tweet a lot with the hashtag "Usada Pekora 5th Anniversary Live"!
ということで！ここからは、みんなお楽しみの、ゲストパート！
And so! From here on, it's the guest part that you've all been waiting for!
今年はどんなお歌が来るのか、お楽しみにーーー！
Look forward to seeing what kind of songs will come this year!
兎神拳に二対一の戦いはない！
There is no two-on-one fight in the Usagi Divine Fist!
覇王はこの鬼神ただ一人！
The Supreme King is only this Kishin!
北兎無双
Hokuto Musou
DESTINY STAR
静寂の闇を 溶かす瞬き
A blink of light melts the darkness of silence...
星座のstory語りかければ
If you speak of the story of the constellations,
それぞれの想い 弾かれるように
their countless thoughts will be like a melody.
男達の旅は 始まる
The journey of men begins.
乾き果てて
Barren and dry...
ひび割れてく時代で
...in an era that cracks apart,
たった１つの 信じるものを
the single thing worth believing in...
追い求めてく
...we continue to pursue.
輝くdestiny star 導かれて
Shine on, destiny star, lead us...
野望の果てまで
...to the end of ambitions.
譲れない願い 向き合う時
When unwavering desires collide,
運命始まる
destiny will play.
(Go straight) 数え切れない
(Go straight) Through the countless...
(Far away) 悲しみを見つめ
...(Far away) tragedies you have witnessed,
光放つ destiny star
let out your light, destiny star.
いつも予言には「答え」しかない
Prophecies only have "the answers,"
辿る道は自分次第で
to follow their path forged by our own hands.
進むべき明日を切り開くよう
To open up the true path to tomorrow,
男達は戦い続ける
men continue to fight.
命さえも
Even if we lose our lives...
投げ出しても構わない
...we do not care.
そう思えるほど 守りたいもの
I've thought this ever since...
見つけた日から
...I found what I wanted to protect.
囁くdestiny star 迷い捨てて
Whisper to me, destiny star, cast aside doubt...
悪夢の果てまで
...to see the end of this nightmare.
一歩も引けない プライドから
I won't back down a step. From my pride...
火花が飛び散る
...sparks scatter.
(Go straight) まだ遠くても
(Go straight) Even if it is still faraway,
(Far away) その手を伸ばして
(Far away) reach your hand out to it,
つかまえてよ destiny star
and catch that destiny star.
絆確かめ 未来の扉
Holding tight to our bonds, we open the door to the future,
開けて旅立つ
and begin our journey.
輝くdestiny star 導かれて
Shine on, destiny star, lead us...
野望の果てまで
...to the end of ambitions.
譲れない願い 向き合う時
When unwavering desires collide,
運命始まる
destiny will play.
(Go straight) 数え切れない
(Go straight) Through the countless...
(Far away) 悲しみを見つめ
...(Far away) tragedies we have witnessed,
光放つ destiny star
let out your light, destiny star.
destiny star
激熱！
[Super Hot!]
チャンスペコ！
Chance peko!
激熱ペコ！！！
Super hot peko!!!
ここらまでじゃ、ぺこの助
This is as far as you go, Pekonosuke.
恨みに歪んだ刃で ぺこーらは斬れぬぺこよ！
You can't cut Pekora down with a blade twisted by hatred!
紅い雫滲む唇に
On the lips that bleed red drops,
ふわり嘆きの霧触れてゆく
the mist of grief casually brushes against them.
空に浮かぶ鏡美しく
The mirror that floats in the sky is beautiful,
遥か暗夜の彼方照らしてる
illuminating the distant night.
降り注ぐ数多の星に想い馳せて
My mind drifts to the countless falling stars,
しめやかに...
keenly...
絆の糸
The bond of fate
強く 強く 結ぶ
Strongly, strongly connecting
瑠璃色に輝く 綺羅の瞳
Eyes shining in lapis lazuli
闇よりの使いに 閉ざされても
Even if sealed by a messenger from the darkness
繋いだ夢の橋 誰も奪えないから
No one can steal the connected bridge of dreams
無限の明日 映して
Reflecting an infinite tomorrow
妖し 光放つ鳴神に
Releasing a mysterious light in the thunderclouds
甘い 言葉の蜜 薫り立つ
The sweet scent of honeyed words rising
密か 黒い鼓翼 忍び寄る
Secretly, stealthily approaching the dark night
心臓 鐘が 行き場求め 喘ぎ出す
My heartbeat moans, seeking a place to go
星霜の 流れに隠す 歪んだ罠
Hidden in the flow of the seasons, twisted traps
艶やかに 鋭い牙を 剥く
Sharply sharpening the elegant fangs
巡る 巡る 悲劇
Revolving, revolving tragedies
玉響に消えゆく 水泡のように
Disappearing into the hazy night like bubbles in the water
儚い刻 辿る運命なら
If destiny follows this fleeting story
曇りなき刃掲げ 清い詩紡ぐ
I'll raise a cloudless blade, weaving a pure song
譲れぬ未来のため
For the sake of an unyielding future
浅い 眠り続く 黎明に
Continuing in a light sleep until dawn
独り 祈り込めて 織り上げた
Offering a solitary prayer
涙 蒼い雲に 刻まれて
Tears engraved in the blue clouds
愛し あなたの影 追いかける
Chasing after your beloved shadow
憎しみの炎渦巻く この地上で
The flames of hatred that swirl on this earth
汚れなき心 貫いてく
Piercing through the pure heart
熱き 熱き 誓い
A passionate, passionate vow
瑠璃色に輝く 綺羅の瞳
Eyes shining in lapis lazuli
闇よりの使いに 閉ざされても
Even if sealed by a messenger from the darkness
繋いだ夢の橋 悠久に綴りゆく
The connected bridge of dreams continues eternally
奏でる奇跡きっと...
Surely playing a miracle...
可能性の兎
[Rabbit of Possibility]
兎田ぺこら 変身まで
[Until Usada Pekora's transformation]
未来ある若者の芽を摘むな！
Don't nip the bud of promising youth!
後ろ向くなお前！前だけ見てろ人生！
Don't look back! Look only forward in life!
ぺこちゃんのことが大好きです
I love you, Peko-chan.
覚醒
[Awakening]
Please hear me
I want to tell you
Please sing to me
I wanna hear your voice
時の鼓動がまだ響く間
While the heartbeat of time is still resonating
While the heartbeat of time still echoes...
裸の言葉胸に閉じ込めた
I locked away naked words in my chest.
記憶の色が滲み始める
The colors of memories begin to seep out
破れた世界の隅で
in a corner of a broken world.
何も求めずにただ抱き寄せる
I pull you close without asking for anything.
今の僕にはそれしか出来ない
That is all I can do now.
震えた強がりでもプライドに見える
Even trembling bravado looks like pride,
逸れた子供のように
like a stray child.
最後の声さえも
Even my final voice...
風がさまようせいで消された
...was erased by the wandering wind.
月に手を向けたまま
With my hand still turned toward the moon,
君は空の星に消えた
you disappeared into the stars in the sky.
「側にいて」と抱きしめても
Even if I hold you tight, saying "stay by my side,"
もう二度と聞こえない君の歌声は
your singing voice that I can't hear ever again
降り注いだ雨のサイレン
is a siren in the pouring rain.
僕の代わりに今この空が泣き続ける
Instead of me, this sky keeps crying now.
これまで踏みつけてきた教えを
The teachings I've trampled on until now...
今掻き集めこの胸に当てても
...even if I gather them up now and press them to my chest,
救い求め歌うようなお遊戯に見える
it looks like a game, singing in search of salvation,
物語る大人のように
like an adult telling a story.
言葉に寄り添うだけの
Empty love and guidance...
空の愛と導きはいらない
...that only snuggle up to words are not needed.
飾られた祈りでは
With decorated prayers,
明日の手掛かりに触れない
I can't touch the clues for tomorrow.
いつか君に届くはずの
That should reach you someday...
名も無き幼い詩が描くわがままを
...the selfishness drawn by a nameless, young poem.
忘れたいよ一度だけ
I want to forget, just once,
眠れぬ悲しみがその詩を抱きしめてる
sleepless sorrow is hugging that poem.
Freezing cold shatters my sorrow
And scorching sand puts it together again
投げ捨てられる正しさなら
If it's a righteousness that can be thrown away,
消える事ない間違いの方が良い
it's better to have a mistake that never disappears.
臆病に隠してた声を今
The voice I hid cowardly, now...
この手でもう一度晒せば良い
...I should just expose it with these hands once more.
掴む軌道も咲く光も
Even the path I grasp and the light that blooms...
乾いた心のせいでモノクロに見えた
...looked monochrome because of my dry heart.
忘れないよ今日の景色を
I won't forget today's scenery,
ありふれた願いが足元を照らしてくれる
a commonplace wish illuminates my feet.
ふぅ... ぺこーら... 一体どうなったぺこ...？
Phew... What on earth happened to Pekora, peko...?
一匹残らず...
Every last one of them...
喰らってやる！
I'll devour them!
漆黒降臨
[Jet-black Descent]
Clawing inside my head
Shredding my self-control
It's getting close to the edge
I'm breaking down
Fragmented memories are glitching in my head
Stuck in a moment and it's burning up bright red
A roaring howl disappears into the night
My soul is here to stay, wow wow wow wow
Fading, I'm losing my grip of sanity
It's changing me
My heartbeat is racing so fast
Unleashing the carnage inside
Don't run away now
I'm just getting started
Hey now
This ain't who I am
Obey now
The voices confuse my mind
Let's go insane now
Look what I've become
Obey now to me
Your hope's gonna turn to fears
When I scream
Corrosive voices laugh and whisper in my head
Tried to ignore 'em but they're calling for a bloodshed
I'm like a puppet, someone's pulling all the strings
Drowning in misery
I can't get out
Breakout this rusted gate
Search and eradicate
Burning the hate from within
Ready to dominate
It's time to liberate
The chaos inside of him, wow wow wow wow
Fading, I'm losing my grip of sanity
Straining me
My heartbeat is racing so fast
Unleashing the carnage inside
Don't run away now
I'm just getting started
Hey now
This ain't who I am
Obey now
The voices confuse my mind
Let's go insane now
Look what I've become
Obey now to me
Your hope's gonna turn to fears
When I scream
Whoa...
ハラペコチャレンジ
Harapeko Challenge
負けないぺこ！
I won't lose, peko!
ほい！
Here!
V獲得
V Acquired
ハラペコドライブ
Harapeko Drive
伝説の朝に
On that morning of legend
誓った言葉
the words we pledged
分かち合う声に
to our shared voice
奇跡よ照らせ
let the miracle illuminate...
革命
Revolution...
Let's shout!
革命を
Revolution...
Let's shout!
革命デュアリズム
[Title: Revolutionary Dualism]
風の舞うヒカリの空
The wind dances through the sky of light
吹き抜ける残響
and the echo blows through.
この右手と
This right hand and...
この左手
this left hand...
何を求める？
what do they wish for?
魂のカタルシスに
Longing for catharsis of the soul,
焦がれた感情
our burning emotions...
重ね合えば
If we place them together,
繋ぎ合えば
connect them to each other,
伝うのか？
will the message come through?
運命に委ね
To surrender to destiny
流れのままに
and just flow along,
変わらぬ明日じゃ
never changing our vision of tomorrow...
面白くない
that's not interesting.
沸騰せよ
Boil away,
血液のレイヴ
rave of blood,
交錯する
mixing together
プラズマのように
as though with plasma.
革命の
Revolution's
デュアリズム
dualism –
さあ始めよう
now, let's begin!
以心伝心 生の咆哮
Does the telepathic roar of life
届いていますか？
reach where you are?
化学反応 愛が伝承
This chemical reaction of love is an epic.
ついてこい 夢の果て
Follow me to the end of the dream!
どんな人生だって
All paths of life
いつかは混じり合う
will merge together someday.
その日 君はジャッジメントする
When that day comes, you will pass judgement.
革命を Let's shout!
Revolution, let's shout!
プラスマイナスが０の
A decent tuning,
悪くはないチューニング
balanced perfectly at zero.
キスみたいに
Like a kiss,
伝染した
it has cracked into my system –
色褪せないドリーム
a forever-colorful dream.
神様は希望与え
The gods grant us hope
痛みを暈して
and obscure the pain.
何を守り
What do I protect?
何を信じ
What do I believe?
生きろと云う？
In your words, how should I live?
未来への扉は
The door to the future
コインのトスさ
is the toss of a coin.
残酷を選べ
Choose cruelty,
暁の君
you of the daybreak.
虹の架かる
I'll show you a flight
見た事ない
above a stunning view,
絶景のフライト
crossing the rainbow as you've never seen.
教えてやる
I'll teach you
覚醒の
awakening's
デュアリズム
dualism –
さあ飛び込もう
now, let's fly in!
百花繚乱 共振る衝動
Emerging legends, howling impulse.
火花を散らして
Send the sparks flying!
胸のブレイブを叩く鼓動
The beats, pounding out your heart's bravery –
どこまで行けるのか？
how far can we go?
変わらない「ナニカ」で
With "something" that has never changed,
なんど信頼した？
how many times have you kissed, have you trusted?
そして君はまた物語に出会う
And then you once again meet a love, a story.
Just trust my heart
Just feel my heart
…hold you
... hold you
誇り高き愛の結晶
Once you have the crystals of prideful love
握りしめたら
tight in your grasp,
迎えにゆくから…
I'll go out to meet you...
刹那から一生さえ
The journey from a moment to our whole lives
すべて見せて来た
was enough to show me everything.
君へのLove song
A love song to you...
Break out! 鎖千切って
Break out! Snap apart your chains!
独立セヨ
Declare your independence!
以心伝心 生の咆哮
Does the telepathic roar of life
届いていますか？
reach where you are?
化学反応 愛が伝承
This chemical reaction of love is an epic.
ついてこい 夢の果て
Follow me to the end of the dream!
どんな人生だって
All paths of life
いつかは混じり合う
will merge together someday.
その日 君はジャッジメントする
When that day comes, you will pass judgement.
革命を Let's shout!
Revolution, let's shout!
ヘブンズペコラッシュ突入ぺこ！
Entering Heavens Peko Rush!
撃ち抜け！
Shoot through!
当たれー！
Come on, hit!
スーパーヘブンズペコラッシュ 突入ペコ！
Super Heaven's Pekorush! Entering, peko!
I have a big gun
I took it from my lord
Sick with justice
I just wanna feel you
I'm your angel
Only a ring away
You make me violate you
No matter who you are
It's all up to you
No one lives forever
Been burn in the hell
By all those pigs out there
It's always been hell
From when I was born
They make me violate them
No matter who they are
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
Have no prayer
So, I keep the gun with me
For my safety
I'll do it with no sweat
They mean business
No time for sissy pig
Queen of ocean
Sing "the Volga" to you
No need to think about it
You do it or you die
Those aren't tears
Don't let it trick on you
I am hard as steel
Get out of my way
Pay back all at once
Suck away the tender part
You made a mess
For Christ's sake, this rotten world
Shit out of luck
Go with my vision
Light up the fire
Right on the power
Weapon... I have it all
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
You made a mess
For Christ's sake, this rotten world
Shit out of luck
Go with my vision
Light up the fire
Right on the power
Weapon... I have it all
皆さん、え～...
Everyone, uh...
今日は発表があります！
Today, I have an announcement!
大チャンス！
A big chance!
PKR48！
PKR48!
ぺこらんだむぶれいん！ 叫んじゃえ
PekorandomBrain! Let's shout!
事件だ 毎日 タイヘン
It's an incident! Every day is hectic!
大成功のタネだと 笑え... 泣いちゃうな 笑え！
It's the seed of great success, so smile... No crying, smile!
もう一回ぴょん！
One more time, pyon!
聞きたくない 言いわけバニー
I don't wanna hear your excuses, bunny!
じたんだの 友情だんだん
Stomping my feet, friendship is building up...
3 2 1 バニバニバニバニマシーナ
3, 2, 1, Bunny Bunny Bunny Bunny Machine!
楽しいトッチが好きなのよ
I love fun slots!
重力シンパシー
[Song: Gravity Sympathy]
すぐ近くんなのに 離れて感じる
Even though you're so close to me, you feel so far away.
君はバスの2つ前の席
You're two seats in front of me on the bus.
声をかけるには ちょっと恥ずかしい
It's a little too embarrassing to call out to you.
何度恋をしても 慣れないね
No matter how many times I fall in love, I never get used to it.
カーブ曲がり 身体が傾く時
When the bus rounds a curve and our bodies lean...
その方向は同じさ
...we both lean in the exact same direction.
君に重力シンパシー 何も話せなくても
Gravity sympathy for you, even if we don't say a word...
確かに今 僕らはひとつになる
...at this moment, we are certainly becoming one.
君に重力シンパシー 後ろ 気づかなくても
Gravity sympathy for you, even if you don't notice me behind you...
わかり合える日が来るよ
...the day we understand each other will come.
窓が曇るほど 乗客は多く
The bus is so crowded that the windows fog up...
君の顔が陰で見えなくなる
...and your face is hidden in the shadows.
喋るその声に 耳を傾けて
I strain my ears to listen to your chatting voice...
僕は胸の奥をときめかせた
...making my heart flutter deep inside.
バスが急に スピード上げた瞬間
The moment the bus suddenly speeds up...
みんな一緒に仰け反った
...everyone falls back together.
愛は重力フレンズ そこにいる それだけで
Love is the gravity of friendship, just by you being there...
二人はそう 地球を共有する
...the two of us share this entire world.
愛は重力フレンズ 存在認知されてなくても
Love is the gravity of friendship, even if you don't know I exist...
そのベクトル進めばいい
...it's fine to just head in that direction.
君に重力シンパシー 何も話せなくても
Gravity sympathy for you, even if we don't say a word...
確かに今 僕らはひとつになる
...at this moment, we are certainly becoming one.
君に重力シンパシー いつか同じ重さで
Gravity sympathy for you, someday, with the exact same gravity...
愛について想うだろう
...you will think about love as well.
みんな、盛り上がっていくぺこよー！
Everyone, let's pump it up, peko!
行くよー！お祭りぺこ！
Here we go! It's a festival, peko!
ラビラビちいさなピットに でっかいアイを交信中
Communicating huge love to a tiny rabbit pit...
ちょっと沼っても許してね！ いったって愛は非効率！
...forgive me if you fall a little too deep! After all, love is inefficient!
花が咲く 夢が咲く 一度きりの物語
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom, in this once-in-a-lifetime story.
ヤマトナデシコいつだって
Yamato Nadeshikos, always...
時代を彩る Dreamer
...dreamers who bring color to the era.
A dreamer coloring the era...
無限の彼方へ
To the infinite beyond!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
Together! Yes!
恋に焦がれてドキドキ
Yearning for love, my heart is pounding!
(ドキドキ)
(Pounding!)
いじわるなんてイヤイヤ
Don't play hard to get, no way!
(イヤイヤ)
(No way!)
とびっきりのスマイルで
With a special, dazzling smile,
あなたを連れてってあげる
I'll take you away with me!
惹かれちゃうのは運命
It must be fate that I'm attracted to you.
(そう！そう！)
(That's right!)
あれもこれも抱きしめてあげる
I'll embrace absolutely everything!
(あげちゃう！)
(I'll give it to you!)
選ぶ道に誇りあれ
May there be pride in the path you choose.
進めば輝く未来
If you move forward, a bright future awaits!
乙女
Maiden's...
心
...heart...
いつだってフェスティバル
...is always a festival!
きらめいて トキメキ届けたい
Shining bright, I want to deliver this heartbeat...
今すぐに
...right now!
高く
Higher...
...and higher!
そびえ立つ壁も
Even the towering walls,
やがて越えてくイメージだけで
I can imagine myself overcoming them!
Let's Go! Let's Go!
花が咲く 夢が咲く
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom!
一度きりの物語
This is a once-in-a-lifetime story.
やがては散り行く運命だから
Since our fate is to eventually scatter and fade,
やるだけやるんです
we have to do all we can!
笑いましょう 声高く
Let's laugh out loud with our voices high!
明日の自分に届けたい
I want to send this to my future self tomorrow.
ヤマトナデシコいつだって
A Yamato Nadeshiko will always...
時代を彩る Dreamer
...be a dreamer coloring the era.
無限の彼方へ
To the infinite beyond!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
Together! Yes!
ワガママだっていいでしょ？
It's okay to be a little selfish, right?
(でしょ？でしょ？)
(Right? Right?)
可愛いって言ってなでなで
Tell me I'm cute and pat my head...
(なでなで)
(Pat my head!)
お気に入りのスカートで
In my favorite skirt,
あなたに飛び込んでみたい
I want to dive right to you!
夢見るだけじゃ足りない
Just dreaming isn't enough.
(だめだめ)
(No way!)
決める時は迷わず行きましょ
When it's time to decide, let's go without hesitation!
(行きましょ！)
(Let's go!)
その手で掴む時まで
Until the moment you grab it with those hands,
未来へ加速して行こう
let's accelerate toward the future!
Destiny
いつか
...someday,
あなたと一緒に
together with you,
永遠に触れてみたい ずっと
I want to touch eternity forever...
憧れです
It's my dream!
涙
Tears...
ハラリ
...falling softly...
こぼれ落ちる日も
Even on the days they overflow,
本気の愛で振り向かせたい
I want to make you look my way with genuine love!
Going! Going!
花と舞い 夢と生き
Dancing with flowers, living with dreams,
重なり合う物語
our stories overlap.
諦めなんて似合わないから
Giving up just doesn't suit us,
やるしかないでしょ
so we just have to do it!
期待から希望へと
From expectations to hope,
願いを鳴り響かせて
let our wishes resound loudly!
ヤマトナデシコきらめいて
A Yamato Nadeshiko, shining bright,
高鳴りを超える Future Soldier
a Future Soldier exceeding our heartbeats!
奇跡を信じて
Believe in miracles!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
Together! Yes!
隠しきれない熱い想いと
With burning feelings that can't be hidden,
今を走れ 走れ
run through the present, run!
負けない誓い一緒に掲げて行こう
Let's raise our unyielding vow together and go!
あれやこれやと艶やかに舞う
Fascinatingly dancing this way and that,
予感に誘われ
invited by a premonition.
情熱は燃えて羽ばたくの
Our passion burns as we spread our wings!
無邪気なままじゃいられない
I can't just stay innocent forever.
切り開いて見つけたいな
I want to carve open a path and find it...
本当も嘘もない私になって
...becoming a version of myself with no truths or lies.
花が咲く 夢が咲く
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom!
一度きりの物語
This is a once-in-a-lifetime story.
やがては散り行く運命だから
Since our fate is to eventually scatter and fade,
やるだけやるんです
we have to do all we can!
笑いましょう 声高く
Let's laugh out loud with our voices high!
明日の自分に届けたい
I want to send this to my future self tomorrow.
ヤマトナデシコいつだって
A Yamato Nadeshiko will always...
時代を彩る Dreamer
...be a dreamer coloring the era.
無限の彼方へ
To the infinite beyond!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
Together! Yes!
隠しきれない熱い想いと
With burning feelings that can't be hidden,
今を走れ 走れ
run through the present, run!
負けない誓い一緒に掲げて行こう
Let's raise our unyielding vow together and go!
あれやこれやと艶やかに舞う
Fascinatingly dancing this way and that,
予感に誘われ
invited by a premonition.
情熱は燃えて羽ばたくの
Our passion burns as we spread our wings!
大好きぺこ
I love you, peko!
歌の中なら
If it's inside a song...
声にいで
Let your voice out...
いいのぺこ
...it's okay, peko!
思い出が強さになった
Our memories became our strength.
君ならは歌えるぺこ
If it's you, you can sing, peko!
今日という過去が生まれて
With the past called "today" being born...
未来にはどうしたいか？
...what is it you want to do in the future?
描くんだ
Draw it!
心からぺこらの...
From the bottom of my heart, Pekora's...
「ありがとう」歌ってあげたいんだ
..."thank you" is what I want to sing to you!
RADIANT FORCE
[Song: RADIANT FORCE]
始まる歌 始まる鼓動
The beginning song, the beginning heartbeat
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
Resound far and wide, sound of hope!
「生きる事」を諦めないと
"I won't give up on living,"
示せ 熱き夢の 幕開けを
show us the curtain rise of this passionate dream!
爆ぜよ/風よ この奇跡に嘘はない
Explode! / Blow, wind! There is no lie in this miracle!
その手は何を掴む為にある？
What are those hands meant to grasp?
たぶん待つだけじゃ叶わない
Surely, simply waiting won't make it come true.
その手は何を守る為にある？
What are those hands meant to protect?
伝う 熱は
The heat that is conveyed...
明日を 輝かす 種火に
...becomes the spark that lights up tomorrow!
さあ新時代へ引き金を引こう
Come, let's pull the trigger toward a new era!
伝説の未来へとカウントダウン
Countdown to a legendary future!
羽撃きは一人じゃない
We are not flapping our wings alone.
過去を 超えた 先に
Beyond the past...
創るべき歴史が咲き燃えてる
...the history we must create is blooming and burning!
絆、心、一つに束ね
Unite our bonds and hearts as one,
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
resound far and wide, sound of hope!
「信ず事」を諦めないと
"I won't give up on believing,"
唄え 可能性に ゼロはない
sing! There is no zero in possibilities!
飛べよ/翔べよ この奇跡に光あれ
Fly! May light shine upon this miracle!
切り裂けまだ見ぬ日に行く為に
Tear it apart to go to the unseen days!
不可能なんて何一つない
There is absolutely no such thing as impossible.
こんなに心強いことはない
There is nothing more reassuring than this.
絶対 絶対 絶対信じ合い
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely believing in each other,
ぶっちぎる
we will break through!
たとえ闇に吸い込まれそうになって
Even if we're about to be sucked into the darkness,
涙さえも血に濡れて苦しくっても
and even if our tears are stained with blood and it's painful...
帰る場所が待っている
...the place to return to is waiting!
集え/守れ/契れ
Gather! / Protect! / Pledge!
勇気の結晶が奇跡なんだ
The crystallization of our courage is the miracle!
願い、祈り、すべてを背負い
Shouldering all our wishes and prayers,
本気を越えた本気の唄
a song of true earnestness that surpasses all limits!
痛みなんて何も怖くない
I'm not afraid of any pain!
滾れ 沸騰せよ このカラダ
Surge! Boil up, this body!
翔べ さあ 闇夜に 稲妻を
Fly! Now, throw lightning into the dark night!
出会い笑い合いそして泣きじゃくり
Meeting, laughing together, and then sobbing...
命の炎も一緒に燃やして
...burning the flame of our lives together!
五感の全部が叫ぶ
All of our five senses are screaming...
愛と 呼べる ほどの
...to the extent that it can be called love,
眩しく煌めいた友の証
the dazzlingly sparkling proof of our friendship!
絆、心、一つに束ね
Unite our bonds and hearts as one...
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
Let the sound of hope resound in the air
「信ず事」を諦めないと
It says to "Never give up on believing"
唄え
Sing!
可能性に
To the possibilities...
ゼロはない
there is no zero.
飛べよ
Fly!
この奇跡に
Within this miracle,
光あれ
let there be light!
ガッハッハッ！
Gahahaha!
コムハワードリゾートへようこそ！
Welcome to Comhaward Resort!
バシバシバシバシ、わしが行く！
Slash, slash, slash... Here I go!
コムハワードとはわしのことだー！
Comhaward is me!
みんな、ライブを見てくれてありぺこー！
Everyone, thank you for watching the live show, peko!
このあと22時15分より、メンバーシップ限定アンコールライブがあるぺこ！
After this, starting at 10:15 PM, we have a membership-only encore live show, peko!
まだまだぺこらのミッション見たいぺこだよね？
You still want to see Pekora's mission, right?
ぺこらも歌も歌いたいしみんなにミッションもっと見てほしい！
Pekora wants to sing more songs and wants everyone to see more of the mission!
なのでぜひとも、遊びに来てぺこ！
So please come and hang out with us, peko!
そして、グッズのおさらいです！
And now, let's review the merch!
1つ目は、
First is...
アクリルパネル！
the Acrylic Panel!
こちらはなんと、ホロライブEnglishのイナちゃんが描き下ろしてくれました！
For this one, Ina-chan from Hololive English drew the illustration!
ありがとうイナ！本当に可愛いぺこら、カッコいいしオシャレだし、ぜひともゲットしてみてぺこな！
Thank you, Ina! It's a really cute Pekora, cool and fashionable. Please make sure to get one, peko!
2つ目は、こちら！
Second is this one!
ランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
Random Acrylic Keychains!
イラストは、マるえり先生に書いてもらいました！
The illustration was drawn by Marueri-sensei!
いや、最高なキーホルダー来ました、こちら！
Wow, such a great keychain has arrived here!
7を、やっぱ3つ揃えたいのが人間のサガなのかな？どうぺこ、なんでしょうか？
I guess it's human nature to want to get three 7s in a row. What do you think, peko?
ぜひとも何が届くか、お楽しみに！
Please look forward to seeing which one you get!
そして、3つ目は、
And third is...
ぺこら直筆の「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ！
the "Uso peko desho..." T-shirt written by Pekora!
大人気の直筆Tシャツ「うそぺこでしょ…」出ました！
The highly popular handwritten T-shirt "Uso peko desho..." is out!
部屋着にね、ぴったりだと思うぺこだし、
I think it's perfect as room wear, peko.
「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツでぜひとも外にお出かけするのも、全然ありぺこだと思うので、
And going outside wearing this T-shirt is also totally fine, peko!
ぜひチェックしてみてください！
So please check it out!
そして、4つ目は、
And fourth is...
トラックジャケット！
the Track Jacket!
キービジュアルのぺこらが着てるのと同じぺこ！
It's the same one Pekora is wearing in the key visual, peko!
ぜひともぺこらとお揃いで着ませんか？
Won't you match with Pekora and wear it?
カッコいいしね、なんかオシャレじゃない？
It looks cool and stylish, doesn't it?
こちらもね、コンビニ行く時でもいいし、それとも遊びに行く時でもいい、部屋着にしてもいい、
This one is also perfect for going to the convenience store, hanging out, or even as room wear.
たくさん着てもらえたら嬉しいぺこな、おチェックな！
I'd be glad if you wear it a lot. Check it out, peko!
そしてこちらのグッズ、フルセットでご購入いただきますと、
And if you purchase the full merch set,
数量限定で、ぺこらの直筆サイン＆複製メッセージ入りポストカードがついてくる！
as a limited-quantity bonus, you'll get a postcard with Pekora's autograph and a printed message!
ぜひともお手に取ってください！
Please make sure to get yours!
いくよ、いくよ、いくよ！
Here we go, here we go, here we go!
いくよ、いくよ、いくよ、いくよ、いくよ！
Go, go, go, go, go!
よしよしよしよし！
Alright, alright, alright!
最高だ！
This is the best!
待っていましたこの瞬間！
I've been waiting for this moment!
いいです、いいです、めちゃめちゃいいです！
Good, good, extremely good!
ハズレ注意！
Watch out for misses!
はっはっはっ！
Hahaha!
おら！おら！おら！
Take that! Take that!
いけいけいけいけ！
Go, go, go, go!
うおー！たのむー！
Whoa! Please!
上がれ！
Go up!
頼むー！
Please!
くれるのか！？
Are you gonna give it to me!?
引いてしまうのか！？
Am I gonna hit it!?
ゴーゴー！
Go, go!
いくぞー！
Let's go!